=Love Lurking=
=الحب الكامن=
=Episode 17=
=الحلقة 17=
Gu Nian!
قو نيان!
Gu Nian,
قو نيان,
you destroyed my eye.
لقد دمرت عيني.
You thought I would let you live?
هل كنت تعتقد أنني سأدعك تعيش؟
They're blank bullets.
إنها رصاصات فارغة.
Do you think I'm stupid enough to give you a gun?
هل تعتقد أنني غبي بما يكفي لأعطيك مسدسًا؟
Now,
الآن،
I want you to watch her
أريدك أن تشاهدها
die in front of you.
يموت أمامك.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Beat him to death.
ضربوه حتى الموت.
Yes, Kun.
نعم جون.
K,
ك,
enjoy yourself.
استمتع بنفسك.
Qian!
تشيان!
Stop it, you guys!
اوقفوها يا شباب!
Kun?
متى؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Gu Nian.
قو نيان.
I'm going to kill you!
سأقتلك!
Kun, the police are here!
كون، الشرطة هنا!
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Go!
يذهب!
Gu Nian, hang in there.
قو نيان، تمسك هناك.
Qian!
تشيان!
Doctor!
طبيب!
♪You overturned the story's ending♪
♪لقد قلبت نهاية القصة♪
♪Love ultimately becomes regret♪
♪الحب في النهاية يصبح ندمًا♪
♪Rain pours all night♪
♪المطر يهطل طوال الليل♪
♪Without your company♪
♪بدون شركتك♪
Gu Nian,
قو نيان,
hang in there.
تمسك هناك.
Gu Nian.
قو نيان.
Gu Nian, don't fall asleep.
قو نيان، لا تنام.
Quick, over here.
سريعًا، إلى هنا.
Sir, please stop.
سيدي، من فضلك توقف.
♪I still can't learn to be brave♪
♪لا أزال غير قادر على تعلم أن أكون شجاعًا♪
♪I decide to wander♪
♪قررت أن أتجول♪
♪I smile to hide the sorrows♪
♪أبتسم لإخفاء الأحزان♪
♪How long must regrets linger♪
♪إلى متى يجب أن تستمر الندمات؟♪
♪I calmly resist♪
♪أقاوم بهدوء♪
♪The loneliness when memories swarm♪
♪الوحدة عندما تتجمع الذكريات♪
♪But time often♪
♪ولكن الوقت في كثير من الأحيان♪
♪Makes me anxious♪
♪يجعلني أشعر بالقلق♪
♪A breeze chills my skin♪
♪نسيمة تبرد بشرتي♪
(I'm sorry.)
(أنا آسف.)
Who is it?
من هذا؟
No!
لا!
(Don't fall for anyone.)
(لا تقع في حب أحد.)
(Or you and those around you will be in danger.)
(أو ستكون أنت ومن حولك في خطر.)
Nian, you're awake.
نيان، أنت مستيقظ.
Wait. I'll call the doctor.
انتظر، سأتصل بالطبيب.
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
We finally captured Kun's gang this time.
لقد تمكنا أخيرا من القبض على عصابة كون هذه المرة.
I believe you'll be back on the police force soon.
أعتقد أنك ستعود إلى قوة الشرطة قريبًا.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
what's the exact relationship between you and Gu Nian?
ما هي العلاقة الدقيقة بينك وبين قو نيان؟
Don't forget your mission.
لا تنسى مهمتك
Being too deeply involved
التورط بشكل عميق للغاية
is not good for either of you.
ليس جيدا لأي منكما.
I understand.
أفهم.
You need to maintain Wei Qing's trust.
يجب عليك الحفاظ على ثقة وي تشينغ.
At your wedding,
في حفل زفافك،
the chemist will definitely show up.
سوف يظهر الكيميائي بالتأكيد.
I can't wait any longer.
لا أستطيع الانتظار لفترة أطول.
I must take initiative.
يجب علي أن آخذ المبادرة.
Why are you in such a hurry?
لماذا أنت في عجلة من أمرك؟
Is it for Gu Nian?
هل هو من أجل قو نيان؟
No.
لا.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
better be careful.
من الأفضل أن تكون حذرا.
Let's go see Dr. Gu later.
دعنا نذهب لرؤية الدكتور جو لاحقًا.
After all, she got hurt because of you.
بعد كل شيء، لقد أصيبت بالأذى بسببك.
Okay.
تمام.
Next.
التالي.
Dr. Gu,
الدكتور جو،
we haven't come to see you since you got hurt.
لم نأتي لرؤيتك منذ أن تعرضت للأذى.
So now we want to check in on you
لذا الآن نريد أن نتحقق من أحوالك
and get a check-up.
والحصول على فحص.
Who needs it?
من يحتاجها؟
It's me.
هذا أنا.
I'm about to marry Qian.
أنا على وشك الزواج من تشيان.
So I'm hoping you can help me get ready.
لذا آمل أن تتمكن من مساعدتي في الاستعداد.
So we can have a cute baby.
حتى نتمكن من الحصول على طفل لطيف.
I'm a physician.
أنا طبيب.
Not a gynecologist.
ليس طبيب أمراض النساء.
But you're the doctor we know.
لكنك الطبيب الذي نعرفه.
Right, Qian?
صواب، تشيان؟
Sorry.
آسف.
We're not that close.
نحن لسنا قريبين إلى هذه الدرجة.
Since Dr. Gu doesn't want to help me,
نظرًا لأن الدكتور جو لا يريد مساعدتي،
let's go, Qian.
دعنا نذهب، تشيان.
Wait.
انتظر.
Don't forget what you promised me.
لا تنسى ما وعدتني به.
If you continue to be indecisive,
إذا واصلت التردد،
I'll hand over the recording.
سأسلمك التسجيل.
What recording?
ما هو التسجيل؟
I suggest you ask Mr. Song.
أقترح عليك أن تسأل السيد سونغ.
(Song Qian, you're a scoundrel.)
(سونغ تشيان، أنت وغد.)
(You need to maintain Wei Qing's trust.)
(يجب عليك الحفاظ على ثقة وي تشينغ.)
(If you continue to be indecisive,)
(إذا استمررت في التردد)
(I'll hand over the recording.)
(سوف أسلمك التسجيل.)
(Come to this place tonight.)
(تعال إلى هذا المكان الليلة.)
Are you sure Zhao Yan is here?
هل أنت متأكد أن تشاو يان هنا؟
I have an appointment with Zhao Yan here tonight.
لدي موعد مع تشاو يان هنا الليلة.
I promised him
لقد وعدته
if he shows up tonight,
إذا ظهر الليلة،
I can keep him safe.
أستطيع أن أبقيه آمنًا.
When will Zhao Yan show up?
متى سوف يظهر تشاو يان؟
Let's wait.
دعونا ننتظر.
I don't have time to waste here with you.
ليس لدي وقت لأضيعه هنا معك.
Are you so impatient with me now?
هل أنت غير صبور معي الآن؟
After him.
بعده.
Zhao Yan is over there.
تشاو يان هناك.
Hurry!
عجل!
He's been hit!
لقد تم ضربه!
It's such a mess!
إنها فوضى كبيرة!
Zhao Yan!
تشاو يان!
Zhao Yan, you can't die.
تشاو يان، لا يمكنك أن تموت.
Zhao Yan, wake up.
تشاو يان، استيقظ.
You can't die.
لا يمكنك أن تموت.
You haven't told me
لم تخبرني
the truth about my mother's death.
الحقيقة حول وفاة والدتي.
Song Qian, call an ambulance. Hurry!
سونغ تشيان، اتصل بالإسعاف. أسرع!
Gu Nian,
قو نيان,
he's dead.
لقد مات.
Impossible. I'm a doctor.
مستحيل. أنا طبيب.
He can't die.
لا يمكنه أن يموت.
I can save him.
أستطيع انقاذه.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Let go of me!
أتركني!
Gu Nian, calm down!
قو نيان، اهدأ!
He's already dead.
لقد مات بالفعل.
Why did this happen?
لماذا حدث هذا؟
I was so close to knowing the truth.
لقد كنت قريبًا جدًا من معرفة الحقيقة.
You're tired.
أنت متعب.
I'll take you home.
سأوصلك إلى المنزل.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Gu Nian.
قو نيان.
Take it easy.
خذها ببساطة.
Nian.
لنا.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm tired.
أنا متعب.
Take me home.
خذنى إلى المنزل.
Okay.
تمام.
Nian, let me walk you inside.
نيان، دعني أدخلك إلى الداخل.
No, it's fine.
لا، إنه بخير.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
how did you know I was there tonight?
كيف عرفت أنني كنت هناك الليلة؟
Weiwei told me you went
ويوي قال لي أنك ذهبت
looking for someone at the bar again.
أبحث عن شخص ما في البار مرة أخرى.
I don't want what happened last time to repeat.
لا أريد أن يتكرر ما حدث في المرة الماضية.
So I went to find you.
لذلك ذهبت للبحث عنك.
Did you find anything?
هل وجدت شيئا؟
Nothing at all.
لا شيء على الإطلاق.
Nian,
لنا،
you seem stressed lately.
يبدو أنك متوتر في الآونة الأخيرة.
Why not come with me to the medical seminar tomorrow?
لماذا لا تأتي معي إلى الندوة الطبية غدا؟
Think of it as relaxing.
فكر في الأمر على أنه استرخاء.
Okay?
تمام؟
Okay.
تمام.
(Why would Zhao Yan give me a card?)
(لماذا يعطيني تشاو يان بطاقة؟)
(What is that sound?)
(ما هذا الصوت؟)
(Gu Nian.)
(قو نيان.)
I don't care who you are.
لا يهمني من أنت.
Get out of my home right now.
اخرج من منزلي الآن.
Gu Nian!
قو نيان!
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Are you hurt anywhere?
هل أنت مصاب في أي مكان؟
Should I call you K
هل يجب أن أناديك ك؟
or Song Qian?
أو سونغ تشيان؟
♪What is secretly stirring♪
♪ما الذي يتحرك سرا♪
♪From your mouth, I find it hard to describe♪
♪من فمك، أجد صعوبة في وصفه♪
♪What praises can disappear in just a second♪
♪ما هي الثناءات التي يمكن أن تختفي في ثانية واحدة♪
♪Vanishing without a trace♪
♪الاختفاء دون أثر♪
♪Waving hands to break free from the splendid cage♪
♪تلويح الأيدي للتحرر من القفص الرائع♪
♪Words against the heart, a pain slashes through the sky♪
♪كلمات ضد القلب، ألم يشق السماء♪
♪Floating into the endless night sky, the wind fierce and strong♪
♪تطفو في سماء الليل اللامتناهية، والرياح شرسة وقوية♪
♪Who is reckless, continuing to lose control, with impunity♪
♪من هو المتهور، الذي يستمر في فقدان السيطرة، مع الإفلات من العقاب♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is pulling the strings behind♪
♪لا أستطيع أن أرى من يسحب الخيوط من الخلف♪
♪The wound still aches, and the memory is not yet over♪
♪الجرح لا يزال يؤلمني، والذكرى لم تنته بعد♪
♪There are two endings, whether you understand or not♪
♪هناك نهايتان، سواء فهمت أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is tracking from behind♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية من يتتبعني من الخلف♪
♪The heart still beats, total blood-red before my eyes♪
♪لا يزال القلب ينبض، أحمر اللون كالدم أمام عيني♪
♪Only one ending remains, whether it helps or not♪
♪تبقى نهاية واحدة فقط، سواء كانت مفيدة أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪